Oh, how is it that my eldest grandson is like that?
They say there are three shamans who have already run away.
Huh?
Oh my, you mean the fourth?
back off, back off
If you stay in the bad smell, it will stink.
A dead person who takes over the body of a living person
How can the living handle it?
Everyone die!
Oh my
Um, is that a person? Are you a ghost?
Is that a person or a ghost?
A lot of people came to see the party today.
Now
Inside Baekjedang Dae-dong, Mokju-si, Gyeonggi-do
Take a good place in your territory
Geumcheon Kang family
Nabi, the eldest son of Gyeongsinsaeng, a famous place for the Lim clan,
I have an illness without a cause
I give you this sincerity
Spirits, please receive this sincerity well.
Please help me get well soon.
Ah, ah, ah, ah!
ruler!
let's go!
Dead man
After all the twelve exorcisms,
The gods of ancestors and messengers were all called and chased away.
It's time to go now
I can't go...
I will feel at ease if I send it to you.
Turn off the alarm
Turn off, alarm!
Find it and destroy it, I!
You're concentrating hard, but you're being disrespectful!
Aunt? It's 7:30
10 minutes to go
No, fairy
10 minutes, it can be transferred within 10 minutes.
You can do it, right?
let's go
Now
Umm
Um, um, um, um!
Um...
ha
Ha, um...
I'm sorry
I don't have time right now
If you can't do a thousand in 10 minutes
I have to give up on you, the dead man.
Are you going?
Because I'm busy with work
What's busier than this exorcism?
There is
very busy work
So, let’s transfer the capital quickly?
You're just fooling me into thinking I'm a ghost!
Where do you sell drugs?
What, isn’t it a school uniform?
I have a midterm exam today
Are you going to take responsibility if I don’t go to college?
What a high school student said
You know what I mean, right?
Your hell is that three degrees heaven
It's out there, my hell!
Right here, right now.
Oh, it's going to be a thousand degrees!
Mr...
Oh, you're late!
Oh, hey!
No
Huh?
nice catch
What is it?
Why are you here?
you were waiting
Me?
why?
Are you asking because you really don’t know?
Without you
I'm last in my class
Taking care of my rank
There's only you
Wow, you're unlucky
Oh my, oh my, oh my
-Why are you late today?
- hey!
I'm right behind you
If it's other people, I'll be angry and in trouble.
In an embarrassing moment
i just laugh
As if comforting myself by saying it’s nothing.
A little forced
But
I can't laugh now
Now, everyone, hands on your head.
The person in the back walks forward
I had a hard time today too
Thank you for your hard work!
Did you mess up a lot?
Oh, that's right
I'm punishing myself
cover sign
What should I do?
I don’t think I’ll be able to go to a 4-year college like this.
What school can you go to with your grades now?
There is only middle school
Hey, Mr.
Sorry, out of habit
Sir, wait and see.
I'm not going to work today, I'm just going to study
Tomorrow's test is
I'll definitely take a good look at it, Mr.
I studied at school today
I'm going late
Ha, you have to come quickly.
my stomach hurts
AC, the light doesn't turn on, really.
I should have gone to my own high school after all.
The facility is a mess
Seongya
A person who walks backwards
I am a person who will die soon due to bad luck.
People should walk like this
Can you give me this?
uh?
I'll give it to you
Remember, this is yours
It will come like this
me, me, me, me
Hey, I saw a ghost!
Water in the bathroom, water ghost!
Yes, it's true
Hmm, my body must be very weak.
But I think I saw something strange.
Another nickname for Park Seong-ah
Last place in all schools in Sleeping Beauty!
It's starting again
Go quickly
- I'm going
- bye
I'll send it to you soon
Just wait a moment
It's a delicious restaurant
It's late
Shaman
Do you run away instead of performing a ritual?
mother
I didn't run away.
Oh my
Would you say it has a pierced mouth?
You don't want to talk?
Oh, what can I do, mother!
What are you going to do?
It's like this, this...
I'm going crazy and jumping up and down
My lovely new daughter!
You know
College?
Unconditionally, 4 years
What about the department? What is your major?
Is there anything you can do when you come out?
I have no thoughts
Because you're going to be a shaman anyway
College?
That's just your greed
For other kids, it may be a goal and opportunity in life, but
That's it for you
It's a useless excuse!
Anyone can wield a double sword?
Do you throw away a sharpened knife to grab a rusty one?
Daughter
You are the perfect match right now.
I'm starving while trying to catch these two rabbits.
Oh, I want to go to the college festival!
Rolling around on the lawn
Eat green onion pancakes and drink makgeolli
Then I just passed the exam
I just got a bachelor's warning, yeah
Until there?
It's a dream
Mother, I, a stranger
Hey, I like calling you a student.
You are a student because you are wearing a school uniform.
Just like other kids
Actually, I'm such a shaman.
I know, me too
I'm just dreaming right now
The dream of being an ordinary kid
So let me stay in the dream a little longer
Can you just take a look at it once?
yes?
Anyway, I'm doing well in Cheongsan Yusu.
Make teaching worthwhile
But let’s make one thing clear
promise to customers
make it a priority
Irresponsible things like today
never again
Do you understand, Seongya?
yes, mother
Well, come in now.
I'm having a hard time finding a job.
don't cry
There's a way
When life faces a crisis and stumbles
People look for shamans
This is already my third business failure.
This thing absolutely has to be money.
People who don't have money want money
When I get off work, only Doa
It's so lonely waiting
Ha, the person who couldn't get married
I want to get married
Don't get lost this time
I hope you come to the right place
People without children
I want to raise a child
I want to be independent
Mom, I miss you
Korea, when are you leaving, me?
How to live long in Korea
Oh, the house didn't sell
I want to buy my own home
- I want to cry
- I want to laugh
The crisis of life
What I want
It comes when it's out of my hands
People envy other people
become unhappy
what you already have in your hand
Look, I want to tell you, but
Actually, even I can't do that.
I envy you all
Except for one category
This is why you shouldn't date based on your feelings.
If you don't look at your heart, what do you look at when dating?
face
Yes?
I guess I just liked your face from the beginning
Even if you change your mind, your face remains the same
What's there to cry about? Nothing changes
What if you don’t like me with that face?
It doesn't matter
I like that face
Shaman, you’ve never been in a relationship, right?
You’ve been single since birth, right?
What's important about the heart?
Something you can't even see
Leave aside the things that are clearly visible, like the face.
I was caught up in something like that and cried and cried.
Oh, I really don't understand.
Isn't it obvious?
How can you like something without a heart?
I do it, I do it just by looking at your face
As my heart says this and that,
I won't be swayed, I
Anyway
Very handsome, but he's a murderer
Do you still do it?
Hey, that's...
No, I just don't see the face.
I see something else too
That's an extreme example.
So?
What else are you going to see besides your face?
Um...
Someone I don't know
I'm crying alone on the side of the road
Why?
I don't know, I'm a stranger
But still
go next to that person
I want you to comfort me, the girl I like is
Isn't it too easy?
How do you get past that? Without recognition
Most just pass by
I guess there's no one to comfort me
I guess there's nothing to cry about
Just passing by
Write...
Ugh, that's enough for the face.
Now, can we just comfort the crying person?
How do you feel?
falling out, falling out of face
Hey, I look pretty good!
Completely eliminated
our new daughter
I'm going to make a lot of money today too
I...
Is this the temple of the Fairy of Heaven and Earth?
yes, that's right
Oh yes, thank you
That's right
Gyeonwoo, let’s go.
The grandson is really
yes, handsome
I hear that a lot.
Yes, that's right
You look so handsome
The last guest is entering.
Please come in
I found it
Oh, you're so handsome
Absolutely my ideal type
Sharp eyes, sharp nose
plump lips
Even when you look at it upside down, you still look good...
Huh?
Wait a minute
Upside down?
Remember, this is yours
It will come like this
Could it be that it was a precognitive dream?
Boy, anyway, where is this law?
Hey...
My grandson is suffering from so much bad luck.
I don't know how many times I've been on the verge of death.
Capable of protecting the human body
Please write me a talisman
Ah...
yes
It's a shame to die
So handsome
Please save my grandson, okay?
But die
The remaining lifespan is at most 37 days
Hey Gyeonwoo
Do you have anything to say?
There is none
Hey there
Grandson?
There's a stranger crying on the street, I'm alone
I saw it by chance while walking down the street.
What are you going to do?
Uh...
The kid I like
You'll be standing next to me, right?
and?
go next to that person
I wish I could comfort you
Just stand there
Until the tears stop
Huh? Won't you comfort me?
What do you think I know?
what did i say
What do I know about him?
But
You can do the standing thing, right?
I don't know but
you passed
Save me
Me, fairy?
I'll save you
no matter what I do
I will stop all bad luck, grandma grandson?
I will keep you alive for three to seven days.
Ah, yes...
yes
goodbye
Come again!
uh?
Save me?
who?
Who?
Ah... that
Aunt
Let's solve the problem!
Kid...
let's stop
Let's go, yeah
Ah, mother!
Cancel the request?
You are my guest.
Do you have the ability to handle it?
There is
That...
If only my mother could help me a little
Hey, you fool
I was trying to save the owner of the brazier house.
Have you forgotten that we almost went to the afterlife together?
At that time...
Huh?
upside down?
You should always have it with you
Okay?
You bastard
Huh?
This...
I shouldn't be here
Huh?
When was the last time you got hit so hard?
You can't stand it anymore and are fluttering around again?
If you stand upside down and come in
From then on, it's an equivalent exchange.
To save his life
You have to risk your life
Can you do it?
So...
With my mother's help...
trying to kill him
I have to face all kinds of evil spirits in the world.
No matter how much I received the general spirit
How do you beat 100:1 or 1,000:1?
Ah, if you just put in a little effort...
Why use your strength?
What is he?
It was love at first sight!
What's wrong again?
Did you fail a lot on the test?
No way...
Did you get 0 points?
I have no strength
I'm not in the mood for jokes
Are you sick?
Come on, come on, hurry up and sit down!
Are you doing well on your tests?
yes
Because everyone will be busy
I'll just get to the point.
Well, a new friend came to our class today.
Huh? Transferring schools during exam period?
The timing is so strange, isn’t it?
Don't talk nonsense, okay?
Because it’s your first time, it will be very unfamiliar.
Please help me adapt well.
- Okay?
- yes!
Hey, Gyeonwoo, come in.
- Wow!
- Wow, handsome.
It's touching
Aren’t you a trainee?
The face is genius
Huh?
Why, Park Seong-ah? What?
Oh, do you know him?
Ah...
no
What, but why are you so surprised?
Do you need attention?
No...
But why did you wake up, nigga
I always lie down and sleep when I sleep
Why, I saw that the transfer student was handsome.
Are your eyes wide open?
Do you want to wake up right away?
Phew, it’s totally South American.
Wow, Seongya.
Hyeri said you were from South America
Hey, Maeng Ju-seung
Aren't you quiet?
Do I look like that?
Hey, he doesn't know what it means.
I can't help but laugh if I know what this means, uh
Seong, what about this South American bird?
To a man, to a man
Me, crazy
Where do you think I saw this?
Park Seong-ah?
I think I saw it, you
Can I say hello?
Uh, uh, well, then
Hello, I'm Bae Gyeon-woo.
Please take care of me
applause
Now, then, Gyeonwoo is at the end.
I can go and sit in an empty seat.
It finished early
Don't think about going somewhere else to play.
Study, study, huh?
The exam isn't over yet
yes
Stay focused until the end, okay?
- There
- I've never seen you.
I saw you for the first time today
Huh?
But what about earlier?
What are you really...
Is that it?
No, I'm not like that.
Then don't laugh at that.
I'm smiling
Bad things don't get better
I didn't recognize the Heaven and Earth Fairy.
Are you just pretending to know?
This is my first time seeing him
Did you take my side?
just?
Cool, is that it?
Isn't that cool?
uh
Is it sexy, then?
uh?
Absolutely my ideal type
But he doesn't have much time left to live?
A person who enters the shaman’s house upside down
Are you saying I'm going to die soon?
I have to make sure I don't die, somehow.
How?
- That's...
-Jojo!
Uh, Jo Hye-ri, why?
Hey, let's be together today
You decided to go ska.
- Did you?
- Oh, what is it? Let's go, okay?
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
Ah... ah
Did you have an appointment?
I should go with Hyeri, then.
Pyoho, I’m going first.
Hey, Park Seong-ah
What I said in class earlier
That's not what I told you to hear
Ah...
You know, class president.
Just pretend you didn't hear it
and what
It's not like I said nothing at all.
Yeah, it's okay, I don't care.
Uh...
Well, I have to go first.
Guys, study hard
hello
Don't be late tomorrow
- I won't accept it.
- Uh
Then don't laugh at that.
I'm smiling
Bad things don't get better
She should be the shaman, not me.
Now, Kyungmin, take it and boldly.
Relax your shoulders
ten
Hey, isn’t this your first time?
There, there, there
Woah, woe, won't you go to the bathroom with me?
Are you crazy because you studied too much?
Take it easy, my friend.
Kid...
Well, don't do that, let's go together just once.
Why is this so disgusting!
Go alone, you bastard!
Lee, Lee...
Just come with me!
You're nice!
To the point where I go to the bathroom with you.
Not nice!
transfer student
What are you doing there?
Can't you hear?
You're not pretending you didn't hear, right?
I, I, pretend not to hear, that.
You hurt me, Mr.
What were you doing here?
Hey friend
Yes?
From earlier
You were watching from here, right?
no
I just came and the one here was a different kid
Hey, this, this
Our friend is feeling well, huh?
Yeah, they say I'm in good shape
I hear it a lot
Right?
Let's do archery
Suddenly?
Friends just make decisions
I make the rest
Huh?
Come to your senses
Does anyone just accept that they are the last ranked team in the country?
wow!
No...
That's not even cheap, huh?
Perfect for archery
Why hasn't this been fixed yet?
Oh, this door is really
Oh, really...
AC
Just don't look at the ceiling, just the ceiling
Really, Mr.
3, 2, 1
If you stand upside down and come in
From then on, it's an equivalent exchange.
To save his life
You have to risk your life
Can you do it?
Even now, the owner of the brazier house
Just transfer it to me, okay?
Huh? no!
Hey
Are you okay?
uh?
Uh...
What about you?
uh?
It's not okay
What are you?
Why are you running in?
uh?
Oh, I'm trying to save you
I heard the sign over there fell down.
But you saved me
I'm sorry. Did you get hurt because of me?
That's enough
don't mind
Man, how can you not care?
I was hurt
Is this really wide?
Or do you have no sense of crisis?
You jump in like this
It's not nice, it's stupid
Did you think I would thank you for coming to save me?
hey!
But I'm thankful, for just saving me
But why aren’t you surprised?
Does this happen often?
Is it always like this?
promise to customers
The first priority is your mother.
This new daughter, I'm just keeping that promise.
I'll be back
yes
Please come in
I tell my mother to always follow the example of the flower spirit.
I heard a lot of words
There's no use saying good-bye
I mean money
Those who are good at using amulets earn the most
Those kids like flower spirits
They don't even ride this jack.
The soles of my feet are so soft
Oh, the soles of those damn feet
ugly soles
Writing a talisman is
The flower doryeong received from the Dragon King is said to be the best.
Yeah?
yes
I'm pretty good at writing...
But yours doesn’t work, I can’t use it.
I don't use it
Why? Why not?
Don't you know?
Your new mother is General Dongcheon.
your mom
knife
You know,
Do you have it?
I wrote a talisman without permission
If you get hit by that knife
Do you think the soles of my feet will remain?
Have you ever been hit on the sole of your foot?
Heung
The person I really want to save
That's because
Man... Is it a man?
Um... do you like it?
Are you really crazy in love?
- Hey, come out, why are you stuck like this?
- ah!
- get in the way
- I'm sorry.
Uh...
Huh?
that's me here
Is this a little disappointing?
- again
- Uh, huh?
- Oh, not this one.
- No, why is this...
- Again, again, again
- You write it, if you're going to do it.
Again!
Hey Gyeonwoo
I save you
Let's go!
He said he collapsed in the men's bathroom.
What, but why is everything wet?
Water ghost...
What happened?
Are you seriously hurt?
What should I do, if I see you lying down?
Oh, what should I do?
It doesn't hurt
Oops, I'm late again
Gyeonwoo, it’s okay now
i did it
I need to save you
Ah...
Why is it in front of my eyes...
Uh, huh?
Uh...
Huh?
I need to sleep
I couldn't sleep at all
Is it true, really?
Gyeonwoo, after the exam
Would you like to go to Kono together?
I am Jo Hye-ri, the second class leader in the second row.
Uh-huh, these really are great!
You don't study for the last exam, huh?
- Would you like to go to the PC room together?
- Let’s go take four pictures for the rest of our lives.
Do you have a girlfriend?
- Star star ID, please.
- Let's go destroy Ashuli.
I won't see ghosts
I can be a good boy
don't abandon me
Don't abandon me...
how long did you sleep
Tsk
Huh?
ah!
Oh, that's right, amulet
Lady, I should have given you an amulet.
My original plan was to just give you a talisman.
Revealing my identity
It was about beating the drum of love.
Boy, it was the best plan.
You said you don’t want your identity revealed?
I heard that’s why you do the blinds too?
Ah, that's a problem when you're a guest.
In front of original love
Because there shouldn’t be anything to hide.
Oh, and that Spider-Man too
You take off your mask when you kiss MJ.
Take off half of it
Did you?
Why did you do that?
Was it because you were embarrassed because it was your first kiss?
Anyway, if you know my new mother,
- Now it's a no-no.
- Ah, I don't know, I don't know.
Is what your mother says always the right answer?
Sometimes I'm right
Why are you stopping me from saving people?
I don't understand, really
Oh no, I don't know
Looks like you have a guest.
Ah
I came to get an amulet
Cheonji Fairy
Hey...
He said he would give me a talisman
What about grandchildren?
Ah...
He doesn't usually come to places like this.
That day too, I forced myself to take it.
Ah...
Then it won't work
Yes?
That...
This talisman
You have to see it in person and hear the explanation.
It's an effective talisman.
The person concerned must be here
By all means
Uh, yeah
It's all in front
Yeah
Huh? Uh, Gyeonwoo.
Ah, you look handsome in the morning too
You look handsome even in the evening, right?
Even if you look at it upside down, you look handsome
Wow, handsome...
huh?
Hey Gyeonwoo
You...
you
Do you die by drowning?
Parkseong ice tea, ah
Park Seong Americano?
Seongya, it’s okay...
I won't see ghosts
You can be a good girl, don't abandon me
Oh, what should I do?
If you can see it clearly like this
There's not even a day left
What is that face?
In that short period of time, bad luck came to me.
But now I only have this talisman...
So how much is it?
uh?
I didn't think about how much I should get?
Would it be too showy if I gave it to you for free?
Baby, confessing with a talisman is
It's a bit like that
The price...
1,000?
2,000?
Or is it 10 million won per piece, making it 100 million won?
Or call it cheap this time
Next time you come back hurt more
Even the exorcism is bundled into a set.
Are you trying to call it expensive?
Ah, Gyeonwoo.
No, what is that?
scammer
Oh my, Gyeonwoo
me, grandma and you
Do you think I saw one or two of the same people?
I have no intention of helping you anyway.
They're just trying to get money.
Where did you carelessly
Spout such nonsense!
What do you think of Heaven and Earth Fairy?
You know what?
Misfortune is contagious
So usually people
They say they don't come around unhappy people.
Even though we do jeokseon, we don't eat together.
But asking me to eat together?
Because there are only fools and fraudsters?
But you're not stupid.
Then you're a scammer
- Let's go, grandma.
- Oh, Gyeonwoo.
Either a fraud or a fool
Think it's the last time and believe it just once
Because I won’t lose anything if I believe in it
What if you believe it?
You lose money and become unhappy.
If you don't believe it
I'm just... unhappy.
Let's go, grandma
Sorry, sorry
The cowherd is destined to drown
The amulet is still in my hand
next 3 weeks
I will protect you unconditionally
Why are you working so hard?
I'm looking for a place to drown
Suddenly?
Oh, what should I do?
too many
More than 100 places
Because I just moved here
I'm sure there are a few places I know of.
Should I just ask where have you been?
Oh, is this too suspicious?
What should I do?
Oh, transfer student?
There are many too
Don't give this to all transfer students.
Give one to the nerd too, hey.
I collapsed in the bathroom yesterday
You were taken to 119.
That's because my body is weak
Write it, no.
I think I saw something
The day before, you saw me
You said we should go to the bathroom together at night?
It's because you're easygoing
you are real
Hey, and no nerds.
why?
Your face doesn't look like Gyeonwoo's
This one was really bad, uh
Uh, this...
New student selection...
What are you scared of?
You probably don’t know that I am a fairy of heaven and earth.
But why is it so wet in here?
huh?
uh?
This is about one piece
Give it to the nerd too, hey
I collapsed in the bathroom yesterday
You were taken to 119.
I saw a water ghost in the bathroom.
hanging from the ceiling
It's so scary to have your mouth completely torn apart.
Come on, sit down quickly.
What is it?
Park Seong-ah, where did you go when you weren’t sleeping?
Where did you go?
I guess he went to the bathroom.
When you meet a water ghost
A person falls into dish water and dies
Do you want to die?
That's right
You don't do bad things in the first place
When you startle me, I want to lose my temper
When I suck at it, I want to catch it and eat it.
That's how you become a demon
don't worry too much
I will make you a Buddha
Instead, I'm not targeting kids anymore, okay?
Now, promise me
promised
Then I'll go now
Ah
Move to the women's bathroom
That way it's easy to transfer the capital
I'm really going, just be quiet
What's the sign, Mr.
There's no one
I was scared for no reason
Hey, light up
Hey, what is this?
huh?
- Is there anyone here?
- Is there anyone?
Oh, what should I do?
Turn off second-hand smoke!
Ah...
-Does it smell good?
- Hey, isn't he dead?
no reaction
- Transfer student?
- Gyeonwoo?
Hey, what's your face?
If that happens, life will be really enjoyable.
It doesn't taste good, it tastes salty
Hey
Have you seen the transfer student’s pose?
No way
IC
Huh?
- Hey, Park Seong-ah.
-What is he?
- What are you doing?
- Why are you out there?
Die quickly!
Oh, oh, oh!
uh?
Uh, huh?
What are you doing?
Uh... that...
That...
You...
Protect...
All three and seven days
It's bad luck that comes at any time.
The guy who already has the ticket to the underworld in his hand
The transfer student said he was an arsonist.
Keep your distance, keep your distance
Poor kid
Are you itching to help?
You say you can't be a murderer even if you're handsome?
But I'm better than others
You see a lot, right?
I don't believe in rumors
I believe what I see
Let's become friends, let's
I just hate all people
I'm going to you from now on
But I will save you
Let's go out, together